<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>configuration on wetware</title>
    <link>/tags/configuration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in configuration on wetware</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, mchaker; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 10:18:38 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/configuration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Comcast Business Static IPv6 Setup on a UniFi Security Gateway</title>
      <link>/post/comcast-static-ipv6-setup-on-unifi-security-gateway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 10:18:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/comcast-static-ipv6-setup-on-unifi-security-gateway/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to mikehanley from the Comcast Business Support Community Forums for the dhcpv6-pd commands.
Setting up IPv6 on a Comcast Business account is not straightforward if you are not using Comcast&amp;rsquo;s combined modem-router.
If you are using a UniFi Security Gateway ( SKU: USG), the following steps are necessary to get IPv6 working:
Assumptions:
 Comcast is providing you a /56 subnet for your IPv6 allocation You are using the UniFi web interface to manage your USG through a Cloud Key or Controller installation eth0 is your WAN interface  The interactive command-line route  In Settings &amp;gt; Networks &amp;gt; WAN, set the WAN interface to DHCPv6 with Prefix Delegation Size to 59 ( why 59 instead of 56) Save the new WAN network settings and wait for the USG to provision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing VMware ESXi on an Intel J1900</title>
      <link>/post/installing-esxi-on-intel-j1900/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 20:18:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/installing-esxi-on-intel-j1900/</guid>
      <description>Attempting to install ESXi on an Intel J1900 results in an error. The boot process freezes on:
 Relocating modules and starting up the kernel&amp;hellip;
 The fix can be found at: an archive of the original blog post
In short,
 At the ESXi boot screen, press Shift+O to open the boot options prompt. In the boot options line that appears, add the following after a space at the end of the line: ignoreHeadless=TRUE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extended Bash History</title>
      <link>/post/extended-bash-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 16:09:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/extended-bash-history/</guid>
      <description>link to original stack overflow post
First, run the following to establish your extended bash history file:
cat ~/.bash_history &amp;gt;&amp;gt; ~/.bash_history_extended I then added the following to my .bashrc:
1 2 3 4  export HISTFILESIZE= export HISTSIZE= export HISTFILE=~/.bash_history_extended PROMPT_COMMAND=&amp;#34;history -a; $PROMPT_COMMAND&amp;#34;   Remember to run source ~/.bashrc in any running shells/terminal windows to get the latest bash history config established.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
